<?xml-stylesheet href="/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</title>
    <link>https://www.ritcct.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://www.ritcct.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 11 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_11/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_11/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_11/ -&lt;p&gt;This week, we&amp;rsquo;ll have the meeting to set up our CampusGroups page and a few other things, so you&amp;rsquo;ll have other places to go for future club information shortly. The old website will come down when this happens, and ritcct.com will redirect to the CampusGroups page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have the same two meetings as usual at 6:30 PM in the MLC student lounge on Wednesday and at 4:00 PM at WAL 4510 on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seeing that we only have a month to hold any potential e-board elections, a form is now also linked right here &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/wh2rFVWVroiDLCub9&#34;&gt;https://forms.gle/wh2rFVWVroiDLCub9&lt;/a&gt;) for you to access to submit your name and a role if you&amp;rsquo;re interested. The President/Vice President role is considered one, and whoever is the runner-up for President will become VP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;General role responsibilities include —&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;President/VP: Oversight, attendance at club meetings. Oversees event planning and the roles of other e-board members, including finances and appointment of the Language Advisor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treasurer: Oversees club finances, conducts fundraising, and keeps financial records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secretary: Keeps attendance lists at club meetings and writes weekly announcement posts describing recent updates and future plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone for the support!&lt;/p&gt;
- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_11/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 10 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_10/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_10/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_10/ -&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re officially pre-approved for club status now, which means that we should be officially and fully recognized as a student organization by next semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides this, we have the usual two meetings at 6:30 PM in the MLC student lounge on Wednesday and at 4:00 PM in WAL 4510 on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuing about e-board roles — since we&amp;rsquo;re now going to be recognized and not every e-board member here now will be here in the fall, we need to elect new e-board positions soon for the upcoming semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, the e-board has five roles: President &amp;amp; Vice President, Secretary, Treasurer, and Language Advisor. The current structure seems to be that President &amp;amp; VP run together, Secretary &amp;amp; Treasurer are elected separately, and then the four-person e-board will appoint a Language Advisor based on club membership later in the semester. If any one of you wants one of these roles, you should totally run! We need candidates!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The election will probably be during our last meeting at the end of April. Even if you aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in a role right now, please consider one — they aren&amp;rsquo;t too much responsibility — they require a few training quizzes to be done on CampusGroups, but after that (so far, anyway) club management has been not too difficult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you Wednesday/Friday!&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_10/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 9 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_9/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_9/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_9/ -&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that spring break is over, we&amp;rsquo;re back with two more meetings this week — one on Wednesday from 6:30 PM - 7:30 PM in the MLC student lounge, and one from 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM in WAL 4510 on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, we&amp;rsquo;ll just have more discussions about anything anyone wants to talk about (but in Mandarin), and then on Friday, we might continue last meeting&amp;rsquo;s rounds of 升級. We could also try something else if anyone&amp;rsquo;s interested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you back! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been to a Wednesday meeting before and you want to, they&amp;rsquo;re new — you should come!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;拜拜！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_9/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 8 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_8/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_8/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_8/ -&lt;p&gt;晚安！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week, we&amp;rsquo;ll have two meetings again — one in the MLC student lounge on the third floor of Eastman on Wednesday beginning at 6:30 PM, and one in WAL 4510 on Friday from 4 to 5 PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Wednesday meeting is just a conversation table for discussion, and on Friday we&amp;rsquo;ll continue with card games like we had last week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you all then!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;那後，春假快樂！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_8/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 7 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_7/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_7/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_7/ -&lt;p&gt;Hi again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of this week, meeting notifications will be sent on Mondays instead of at the end of the week, and we&amp;rsquo;ll have plans ready further in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week, there will be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Board games at the MLC student lounge, 6:30 PM on Wednesday (Feb 26)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poker/card games at WAL 4510, 4:00 PM on Friday (Feb 28)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can view our calendar at &lt;a href=&#34;https://pastecal.com/8P47KLUH?view=month&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any ideas, we&amp;rsquo;ll totally add them in advance. We&amp;rsquo;re trying to keep everything planned a month ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;祝好！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_7/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 6 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_6/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_6/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_6/ -&lt;p&gt;你們好！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week&amp;rsquo;s meeting will happen as usual from 4-5 PM in WAL 4510.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the announcements for tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s meeting, we also have a few new things to talk about — first, we have a new suggestions form &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/CgzHqhARVd1Xv9SR9&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; where you can suggest things for us to do next meeting if you have any ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t have any suggestions as of yet, so we can try Jackbox Talking Points again (or maybe another one of those games), or maybe Mafia/the group circle game where you have to find the killer (we did that once last semester and it was pretty fun).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, we&amp;rsquo;ve also got a new second meeting happening weekly in the MLC student lounge — on the third floor of Eastman — which will begin next week on Wednesday. These meetings will be mostly just group discussion, board games or studying, and other things that we can fit on one table (the MLC lounge is a little bit smaller than our usual meeting place).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have a new calendar that you can use to track when we hold events (this will have all of the regularly scheduled weekly meetings as well as other events that we might decide to hold). The link is &lt;a href=&#34;https://pastecal.com/8P47KLUH?date=2025-02-15&amp;amp;view=month&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you all tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_6/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 5 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_5/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_5/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_5/ -&lt;p&gt;This week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to continue to do the same kinds of conversation practice and group activities that we&amp;rsquo;ve been running for the past few weeks. We&amp;rsquo;ll be in the same place at the same time (WAL 4510 from 4 PM to 5 PM).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve run the second When2Meet for this semester for a little while, now, and it looks like we&amp;rsquo;re not going to be able to find a single time that works for everyone. So, as of next week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to start meeting twice a week — once during the normal meeting time, and then a second group study session at 6:30 on Wednesdays. We still don&amp;rsquo;t have room-booking capacity, so for choosing a place, we should pick somewhere public — like RITz or the first floor of the library. You can vote for a location &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/Mu4xpis79CQLYLf86&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, we&amp;rsquo;re going to start instituting a mailing list based on the attendance form that we put up on the board during the normal Friday meetings. If you filled out the form at the last meeting, you should be getting this notification via email, and in the next attendance form there will be an opt-in checkbox so that you can confirm whether or not you would like to continue to receive these messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We should also start sending these out sooner and with more information once we start formulating more detailed plans for future meetings and event ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;希望明天见！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_5/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 4 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_4/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_4/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_4/ -&lt;p&gt;While we&amp;rsquo;re still waiting to be able to make a few changes to our scheduling, location, and advertisement — we have a new poster that we&amp;rsquo;ll start hanging on boards around campus once we&amp;rsquo;re (hopefully) officialized — at the moment, we&amp;rsquo;re still in WAL 4510 from 4-5PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As far as activities go, we still have board and card games, and any that you might have and want to bring are welcome too — especially video games, like Jackbox games, which might be a little bit more fun &amp;amp; engaging than the separate group activities that we&amp;rsquo;ve tried before. Last week&amp;rsquo;s Google Slides presentation practice was interesting, but trying the same idea with Talking Points from Jackbox Party Pack 7 might be even better. If you have a copy of that game and want to bring it, you definitely can — if not, we&amp;rsquo;ll probably have to invest the thirty dollars sometime soon, because this seems like a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve also got decorations and some food to bring to meetings now to liven the mood a little bit — the room&amp;rsquo;s felt a little bit bare these past few weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve got a table runner and a little basket to put White Rabbit in. I hear that we might also have pineapple cakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing that&amp;rsquo;s important to mention (and is also waiting on our pending recognition) is e-board selection for the fall. The positions that we need to fill are president, secretary, and treasurer, and at the moment our five-person group is mostly driving on enthusiasm &amp;amp; vision (if you&amp;rsquo;re good at Mandarin — unlike me — and want to see the club succeed, please consider running for e-board! It&amp;rsquo;s not that hard — we don&amp;rsquo;t do that much — just make flyers and send out announcements every once in a while!). We&amp;rsquo;ll start assembling a ballot and put out a poll sometime before the end of the semester, but this is a long-term goal at the moment to be accomplished before the end of the semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, we have some forms up on the site here — one at the &amp;ldquo;suggestions&amp;rdquo; tab above — including a When2Meet, which you can find &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.when2meet.com/?28725888-ovfHz&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If you want to decide when our new time will be, make sure to fill it out!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;非常感謝，大家！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;明天見！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_4/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 3 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_3/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_3/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_3/ -&lt;p&gt;This week&amp;rsquo;s meeting will run similarly to last week&amp;rsquo;s, because a lot of people are probably going to go to the New Year&amp;rsquo;s celebration events happening around campus — if you want to show up, we&amp;rsquo;ll be in WAL 4510 again from 4:00-5:00PM. Since we might have a smaller group, we&amp;rsquo;ll try to think of activities that can get us all doing the same thing (i.e. one-minute introductions).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One idea that could be fun is giving everybody 15 minutes to create a presentation full of random pictures (put in whatever you want, as long as there are no words and it&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable length) and then trading presentations between people and having them improvise and give the presentation (in Mandarin, of course). If we have enough agreement that this is a good idea, we might try that this Friday (and if it&amp;rsquo;s successful, we&amp;rsquo;ll definitely do it again later).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re (hopefully) close to recognition as a real student organization. The relevant people meet today to decide our fate, and if the news is good, you&amp;rsquo;ll definitely hear about it! After this, we&amp;rsquo;ll have to put together a CampusGroups presence and put together resources for advertising ourselves (better flyers in designated posting areas around campus, presences at club fairs, and whatever else we can do).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we have our own club recognition, too, we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to have more freedom in booking rooms to the schedules of people who&amp;rsquo;d like to show up to meetings. We already have our 4:00-5:00PM room &amp;amp; time set for the near future, but we have a new When2Meet (at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.when2meet.com/?28725888-ovfHz&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;) that we&amp;rsquo;ll use to decide if we should try to work to change meeting times later on. If you want to show up, please make sure to fill this out soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for checking in — wishing you all a fantastic second day of the year of the wood snake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;再见！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_3/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 2 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_2/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_2/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_2/ -&lt;p&gt;There isn&amp;rsquo;t much new information to add for tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s meeting because we planned it out last week — we&amp;rsquo;re still going to bring board games, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be meeting in WAL 4510 on Friday, January 24, from 4:00–5:00PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re going to have Chinese chess (象棋) and Catan, probably at least a few decks of cards, and whichever other board games anyone attending might have and want to bring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is looking, though, like as we try to build the club and gain membership, we&amp;rsquo;re running into scheduling troubles — right now, on the When2Meet for this semester (which is still open, linked on the &amp;ldquo;About&amp;rdquo; tab, if you would like to change your response or fill it out if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already), there isn&amp;rsquo;t one single time that everyone is available, so we&amp;rsquo;ve been discussing introducing some ways that we can have asynchronous club engagement in addition to the in-person meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of now, ideas include a Minecraft server &amp;amp; some more regularly-scheduled voice chatting on the Discord — as of now, it seems like the only two voice channels we have go mostly unused. We can definitely add more features/roles/channels to the Discord server as we gain membership in order to make it a better off-hours meeting environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re going to need to begin working on a system for polling to decide a lot of these questions (most likely Google Forms on this site), so check back to the announcements page soon for more information on what we&amp;rsquo;re planning on coordinating for future plans and projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;明天見！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_2/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss> 