<?xml-stylesheet href="/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</title>
    <link>https://www.ritcct.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://www.ritcct.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>Week 1 [2245]</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_1/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_1/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_1/ -&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the new semester! It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile — if you were on the mailing list, you should&amp;rsquo;ve received an email to let you know that from now on, updates will be made on this web site. If anyone you know is interested, point them here!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, the When2Meet from last semester has been gathering potential time slots, and we&amp;rsquo;re converging on Fridays, from 4:00-5:00PM. We&amp;rsquo;ve booked the rooms as of today, and this is WAL 4510 for all meetings this semester.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also a few changes in the activities and meeting styles that we&amp;rsquo;re planning on instituting now that our meetings are growing — we&amp;rsquo;ll try to gather board games to have available at every meeting. So far, we&amp;rsquo;re planning on bringing Catan, Go, Chinese chess (which will probably require an explainer, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I have no clue what it is either).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll have a deck of cards and probably an assortment of other things once other people start coming and bringing their own — feel free to bring any games you might have. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss having a future movie night — feel free to give movie ideas!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this being said, our inaugural meeting for the semester will be held next Friday, January 24 (we weren&amp;rsquo;t on-time to get rooms booked for this Friday, so it will be one more week until we begin).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;and, one more thing — Lunar New Year is coming soon. If you have any ideas or plans for what we could do related to this either at our first or second meetings, they&amp;rsquo;d absolutely be welcome. We don&amp;rsquo;t have anything set in place at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, 好好學中文！&lt;/p&gt;- https://www.ritcct.com/posts/2245_week_1/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
    
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://www.ritcct.com/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.ritcct.com/about/</guid>
        <description>中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table https://www.ritcct.com/about/ -&lt;p&gt;欢迎！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Chinese Conversation Table is a student group for getting together, practicing language skills and vocabulary, sharing information, and discussing topics about the greater Chinese-speaking world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now, we meet for conversation at 6:30 PM at the MLC student lounge each Wednesday, and for group activities between 4 PM and 5 PM in WAL 4510 every Friday. For more information, join the Discord server linked in the navbar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On our site you can find announcements and our calendar. Each week, we broadcast the time, place, and plans for our upcoming meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any suggestions, just show up with them or fill out the suggestions form — new ideas are always welcome. Thank you for your interest!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;谢谢你看一看！&lt;/p&gt;
- https://www.ritcct.com/about/ - 中文角 RIT Chinese Conversation Table</description>
        </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss> 